infogram.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy - Infogram

## Effective as of: May 25, 2018

## Introduction

Infogram (“Infogram,” “us,” or “we”) respects the privacy and personal information of the members of the Infogram community. This privacy policy applies to all of the services offered by Infogram, including the Infogram website (Infogram.com, Infogr.am), and mobile device software, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this privacy policy.

Collectively, the services covered by this privacy policy are referred to herein as the “Services.” This privacy policy, explains what information we collect from you, how we use that information, how you can review or change the personal information you provided to us, when this policy is effective, how we may change this policy, and the steps we take to ensure that your personal information is protected. We share your personal information only with your consent or as described in this policy.

In specific cases, we use the term **“Designated Countries”** to refer to countries in the European Union (EU), European Economic Area (EEA), and Switzerland.

### Data Controller and Contracting Parties

Infogram will be the controller of your personal information provided to, or collected by or for, or processed in connection with, our Services. The Terms of Use, together with the other policies and agreements listed therein, are between you and Infogram. In the case of content information you provide (see “Content Information” section below) you control such information, you should be solely liable for it and it is outside our control.

As a registered user or site visitor, the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to this Privacy Policy and updates.

### Changes to the policy

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time, and if we make material changes to it, we will provide notice through the Services, or by other appropriate means.

Your continued use of our Services after a revised privacy policy is posted will constitute your acknowledgement that the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to the updated policy. The “effective date” of this policy is referenced and displayed at the beginning of this policy.

## Information We Collect

### Information You Share

#### Account Information

You don’t have to create an account to use some of our service features, such as searching and viewing public infographics. If you do choose to create an account and become a member, you must provide us with some personal data so that we can provide our services to you including your name, email address and/or phone number, occupation, title and a password.

#### Payment Information

In order to gain access to specific premium features within our Services, you must provide us with payment information, including your credit or debit card number, card expiration date, CVV code, and billing address.

#### Support Information

The Services also include our customer support, where you may choose to submit information regarding a problem you are experiencing. For example, if you designate yourself as a technical contact, open a support ticket, speak to one of our representatives directly or otherwise engage with our support team, you will be asked to provide contact information, a summary of the problem you are experiencing, and any other documentation, screenshots or information that would be helpful in resolving the issue.

#### Survey Information

From time to time, we may ask our registered users or visitors to participate in surveys. These surveys are optional. If you choose to participate, any information you provide to us, including personal information, will be linked with your account in our system. If you would not like your information to be used in this way, you have the option to not participate in surveys or, if you do participate, to provide us only with information you consent to our use of in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### Content Information (User Content)

Parts of our Services allow users to upload user content, including infographics, messages, comments, images, and other materials. If you choose to upload personal information through these means in a manner that makes it visible to the public, we will consider that information public and will not limit its use or disclosure in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. We do not associate content information that is stored in your infographics or other free-form content inputs, such as comments, with personal information about you or others. Information in your infographics and infographics belongs to you, and you are responsible for it, as well as for making sure that your content complies with our [Terms of Service.](https://infogram.com/terms) Our employees do not access private content unless required to for security or maintenance, or for support reasons, or with your consent.

If your content is made public, anyone (including us) may view its contents and potentially make other uses of it. If you have included private or sensitive information in your public infographic, such as email addresses, that information may be indexed by search engines or used by third parties. If your user content is shared privately, those you have shared it with may use it in a manner inconsistent with our Terms of Use, and/or inconsistent with your wishes, including disclosing it publicly. 

### Information You Share About Others

#### Contact Information

Some components of the Services allow you and others to share user content and send personal messages with other registered users and non-registered users. To use this feature, you must provide us with personal information about others including an email address for each recipient. For example, when collaborating on a infographic you may want feedback from other team members or non-team members and you can do so by adding those members as collaborators.

### Additional Information We Receive About You

#### Use of the Services

We receive information when you view content on or otherwise interact with the Services, even if you are a visitor. For example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, interact with our email notifications, or visit a third-party service that includes content from our Services, we may receive information about you, or combine such information with other personal information. This service usage information includes data such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited within our Services, location, your mobile carrier, device information (including device and application IDs), search terms, and cookie information.

#### Services you link to your account

We receive information about you when you or your administrator integrate or link a third-party service with our Services, including information from the third party who provides the linked service. For example, if you create an account or log into the Services using your Google credentials, we receive your name and email address as permitted by your Google profile settings in order to authenticate you. We also provide options within the Services that enable you to link to services such as Slack and Salesforce, so you can receive real time notifications and integrate content within those platforms. To learn more about these third parties’ privacy practices, please consult their privacy policies.

#### Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Similar Technologies

A cookie is a small amount of information that a website you visit stores on your computer or device. Like many websites, we, our service providers, linked services, and third party content that appears on our Services may use cookies to collect additional website usage data and to operate our Services. Cookies are not required for many parts of our Services such as viewing public content. You can control at any time what cookies you allow through your browser settings and other tools. However, some of our Services may not function properly if you disable cookies. When your browser or device allows it, we use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, and to monitor aggregate usage patterns.

The Services, our service providers, linked services, and third party content that appears on our Services may use other tracking tools, including so-called “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “web bugs,” “clear GIFs,” etc. (collectively “Web Beacons”) to collect information about your activities on the Services. These are small electronic images embedded in web content and email messages and are ordinarily not visible to users. Like cookies, Web Beacons enable us and our service providers to track pages and content accessed and viewed by users. Also, when we send HTML-formatted (as opposed to plain text) emails to you, Web Beacons may be embedded in such emails to allow us to monitor readership levels so that we can identify aggregate trends and individual usage to provide our audiences with more relevant content or offers. Web Beacons in emails may recognize activities such as when an email was opened, how many times an email was forwarded, which links in the email were clicked, etc. Web Beacons cannot be declined when delivered via a regular web page. However, Web Beacons can be refused when delivered via email. If you do not wish to receive Web Beacons via email, you will need to disable HTML images or refuse HTML (select Text only) emails via your email software

Subject to your settings, if you view or click on an advertisement that we have placed on our Services, or the site of a third party, the ad provider will learn that someone visited the page that displayed the ad, may receive information about you such as your IP address, and may through that information or the use of other mechanisms such as cookies be able to personally identify you. Our advertising partners may share information they collect in connection with our advertising, including personal information, with us. 

#### Our Partners and Service Providers

Infogram relies on a number of other companies, agents, and/or contractors to perform services on our behalf and to assist us in operating and providing the Services to you. For example, we may engage such service providers to provide marketing, communications, website hosting, infrastructure and IT services, to personalize and optimize the Services, provide customer service, collect debts, and analyze and enhance data. In the course of providing such services to us, these companies may obtain information about you, including personal information, and that information will be shared with us. We do not authorize these companies to use or disclose your personal information except in connection with providing the services we request from them.

One of our service providers is Google Analytics, which collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. To learn more about how Google Analytics collects and uses your data when you use the Service, and how you can control the information sent to Google Analytics, please review https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.

#### Do Not Track Signals

At this time, the Services do not respond to “do not track” signals sent from web browsers.

#### Other

Our Services are dynamic, and we often introduce new features, which may require the collection of new information. If we collect materially different personal information or materially change how we use your data, we will notify you and may also modify this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Do Not Collect

We do not intentionally collect information from registered users or visitors under the age of 13. We do not intentionally collect sensitive personal information, such as social security numbers, genetic data, health information, or religious information. Although we do not request or intentionally collect any sensitive personal information, we realize that you might store this kind of information in your account, such as in a infographic. If you store any sensitive personal information on our servers, you are consenting to our storage, processing and use of that information in accordance with this privacy policy.

## How We Use Your Information

How we use the information we collect depends in part on which Services you use, how you use them, and any preferences you have communicated to us. Below are the specific purposes for which we use the information we collect about you.

### To Provide the Services

We use the information we collect including account, payment, contact, and support information to provide the Services to you, including to process transactions with you, authenticate you when you log in, provide customer support, and operate and maintain the Services.

We also use service usage information to operate our services and ensure their secure, reliable, and robust performance. For example, we use the information to protect the security of accounts and to determine what content is popular on our services.

### For Developing Services and Research

We use the information we collect including account, service usage and survey information to conduct research and development for the further development of our Services in order to provide the Services to you and others.

We use collective learnings about how people use our Services and feedback provided directly to us to troubleshoot and to identify trends, usage, activity patterns and areas for integration and improvement of the Services. In some cases, we apply these learnings across our Services to improve and develop similar features or to better integrate the services you use. We also test and analyze certain new features with some users before rolling the feature out to all users.

#### Aggregate Insights

We may also use the information we collect to produce and share aggregated insights that do not identify you. For example, we may choose to publish statistics regarding how many members live in the U.S. versus how many live in Europe. If you complete a survey that asks for employment information, we may publish statistics regarding which professions are most likely to use or not use our Services.

#### Personalized Experiences

Within our Services, we include tailored features that personalize your experience, enhance your productivity, and improve your ability to collaborate effectively with others by automatically analyzing your activities and those of your team to provide better content, notifications, and recommendations that are most relevant for you and your team. For example, we may use your email domain to infer your affiliation with a particular organization or industry to personalize the content and experience you receive on our websites and/or communications. Where you use multiple Services (e.g., Infogram on the web or mobile device), we combine information about you and your activities to provide an integrated experience, such as to allow you to find information from one Service while searching from another or to present relevant information as you travel across our websites.

### To Communicate with you

#### Services Communications

We use the information we collect, including account and contact information to send communications via email, phone and within the Services, including confirming your purchases, reminding you of subscription expirations, responding to your comments, questions and requests, providing customer support, and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and administrative messages. We send you email notifications when you or others interact with you on the Services, for example, when you are @mentioned on a comment. We also provide tailored communications based on your activity and interactions with us. For example, certain actions you take in the Services may automatically trigger a feature or third-party app suggestion within the Services that would make that task easier. We also send you communications as you onboard to a particular Service to help you become more proficient in using that Service. These communications are part of the Services and in most cases you cannot opt out of them. If an opt out is available, you will find that option within the communication itself or in your account settings.

#### Marketing

We use the information we collect, including account, contact, service usage and survey information to send you information or materials via email about products, offers, and news we think might interest you. In specific cases where we have your consent and you have provided us additional contact information, we may contact you through other channels including telephone. These communications are aimed at driving engagement and maximizing what you get out of the Services, including information about new features, survey requests, newsletters, and events we think may be of interest to you. We also communicate with you about new product offers, promotions and contests of Infogram or its licensees or selected commercial partners. You can control whether you receive these communications as described below under "Your Choices & Obligations" section.

### For Customer Support

We use the information we collect, including service usage information (which can include your communications) to investigate, respond to and resolve complaints and Service issues (e.g., bugs).

### For Advertising

We use the information we collect, including account and contact information to target ads to registered users, visitors and others through a variety of advertising partners. In some cases we also use information including service usage information, and information from web beacons, pixels, and cookies, and device identifiers that we collect as mentioned above to better understand how to promote and advertise our Services to you.

For example, we use Facebook Custom Audiences to promote specific Services on Facebook’s ad platform. We will only use these advertising partners to promote our Services. We do not promote other products or services that are not related to Infogram.

### For Safety and Security

We use the information we collect, including account, payment and service usage information (including your communications) to verify accounts and activity, to monitor suspicious or fraudulent activity and to identify violations of Service policies including our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy and/or attempts to harm our Members or Visitors.

### To Protect Legitimate Interests and Legal Rights

Where required by law or where we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, legitimate interests and those of others, we may use or disclose information about you in connection with legal claims, compliance, regulatory, and audit functions, and in connection with the acquisition, merger or sale of a business.

### With Your Consent

We use information about you where you have given us consent to do so for a specific purpose not listed above. For example, we may publish testimonials or featured customer stories to promote the Services, with your permission. 

## How We Share Information

We make collaboration tools, and we want them to work well for you. We share information we collect in the ways discussed below.

### Within Our Services

#### Collaborating With Others

Within our Services you can create content, which may contain account and contact information, and grant permission to others to see, share, edit, copy and download that content based on settings you or your administrator (if applicable) select. Some of the collaboration features of the Services display some or all of your profile information to other Service users when you share or interact with specific content. You can confirm whether certain Service properties are publicly visible from within the Services or by contacting the relevant administrator.

#### Sharing of Public Content

We enable the sharing of user content on our Services. If your content is public-facing, third parties may access and use it. We do not sell that content; it is yours. However, we do allow third parties, such as search engines (e.g., Google), archives, and other members of the public to access and compile public-facing information.

#### Managed accounts and administrators

If you register for or access the Services using an account that is associated with a team or organization, information about you including your account, service usage, and user content will be accessible to that organization’s administrator. In order to enable sharing and collaboration within an organization we also share your account information with other registered users within the same organization. In the case of team accounts, depending on the contractual agreement, we may be considered as a processor of the personal information and the organization and it’s administrator would be the controller of such data.

#### Community Forums

Our websites offer publicly accessible blogs, and forums. You should be aware that any information you provide on these websites - including profile information associated with the account you use to post the information - may be read, collected, and used by any member of the public who accesses these websites. Your posts and certain profile information may remain even after you terminate your account. We urge you to consider the sensitivity of any information you input into these Services.

### Sharing with Third Parties

#### Service Providers

We use others to help us provide our Services. This includes to help us do application development, hosting, maintenance, backup, storage, virtual infrastructure, payment processing, marketing and analysis. Third-party service providers have access to your information as reasonably necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for other purposes. All our service providers must meet our security and privacy standards before they gain access to any of your information.

#### Our Partners

We work with third parties who provide consulting, sales, and technical services to deliver and implement customer solutions around the Services. We may share your information with these third parties in connection with their services, such as to assist with billing and collections, to provide localized support, and to provide customizations. We may also share information with third parties where you have agreed to that sharing.

#### Advertising Partners

We work with several third-party advertisers and/or ad networks, to place ads promoting our Services on their platforms. The types of information we share with advertising partners include: device identifiers (e.g., session information) or your contact information based on your consent. You can control whether we may share this information with our advertising partners as described below under "Your Choices & Obligations" section.

#### Linked Services

In the event you opt to link your account with third-party services, personal information including account information (e.g., full name, email address, username) will become available to them. The sharing and use of that personal information will be described in, or linked to, a consent screen when you opt to link the accounts.

#### With your consent

We share information about you with third parties when you give us consent to do so.

#### Law, Harm, and the Public Interest

We may share information about you with a third party if we believe that sharing is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, including to meet national security requirements, (b) enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) protect the security or integrity of our Services, (d) protect us, our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (e) respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person.

#### Prezi Inc. Companies

Infogram is an affiliate of Prezi Inc. This means, we share information we have about you with Prezi Inc. in order to operate and improve products and services and to offer other Prezi Inc. affiliated services to you.

#### Business Transfers

We may share or transfer information we collect under this privacy policy in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Services if a transaction takes place, as well as any choices you may have regarding your information.

## Your Choices & Obligations

### Options to Access and Control Your Personal Information

We provide many choices about the collection, use and sharing of your data, including deleting or correcting data you include in your profile, and controlling the visibility of your content.

#### Update or Correct Data

You can edit some of your personal information through your account. You can also ask us to change, update or fix your data in certain cases, particularly if it’s inaccurate.

#### Delete Data

You can ask us to erase or delete your personal information. In some cases (for example, information previously posted in public areas) it may not be practical, or may be unduly burdensome, to delete user data. In the event that we may not delete your information we will inform you.

#### Object to, or Limit or Restrict, Use of Data

You can ask us to stop using all or some of your personal data (e.g., if we have no legal right to keep using it) or to limit our use of it (e.g., if your personal data is inaccurate or unlawfully held).

#### Access and/or Take Your Data

You can ask us for a copy of your personal data and can ask for a copy of personal data you provided in machine readable form. Registered users and Visitors can learn more about how to make these requests here. You may also contact us using the contact information below, and we will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the “Shine the Light” law, permits members of our community who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we may have disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, including the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made once a year and are free of charge. If you would like to make a request pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, you must do so in writing via email; please include the phrase “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message.

### Account Closure

You may cancel your account and you may opt out of receiving marketing emails from us at any time. In order to cancel your account, opt out of, or modify your personal information, you must do so by logging in and visiting your Settings & Account page and following the instructions provided, or go to our [Help & Support page.](https://support.infogram.com/hc/en-us/articles/360001462693) We encourage you promptly to update your personal information when it changes. Information concerning your past behavior with the Services may be retained by us as long as necessary for the purposes set out above.

Please note that although you may opt out of receiving certain emails, we reserve the right to communicate with you via email regarding specific products and services you have ordered, requested, or inquired about.

### Additional Rights of Members or Visitors from Designated Countries

Members and visitors in the Designated Countries may have additional rights under their laws. Click here to learn more.

## How We Secure and Store Your Information

### General Security

In order to protect both the personal information and the general information that we receive from you through your use of the Services, we have implemented various security measures. For example, when you enter personal information (such as your contact information) on our online forms, we encrypt that information using transport layer security (TLS). We also follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

### Risk of Interception

Please keep in mind, however, that whenever you give out personal information online there is a risk that third parties may intercept and use that information. While Infogram strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. We cannot guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through your use of the Services, and any personal information, general information, or other data or information is provided to us at your own risk.

### How Long We Keep Your Information

We will only retain your information to the extent: (a) it is needed for the purposes which we have conveyed to you; (b) we are required by law to maintain such information; or (c) it is needed for us to address any issues or inquiries that you may have. When your information is no longer required, we will dispose of such information by destroying it or erasing it.

### Cross-Border Data Transfers

We process data both inside and outside of the United States and rely on legally-provided mechanisms to lawfully transfer data across borders.

Some of the third parties described in this privacy policy, which provide services to us under contract, are based in other countries that may not have equivalent privacy and data protection laws to the country in which you reside. When we share information of our users in the Designated Countries, we make use of European Commission-approved standard contractual data protection clauses, binding corporate rules for transfers to data processors, or other appropriate legal mechanisms to safeguard the transfer.

Countries where we process data may have laws which are different, and potentially not as protective, as the laws of your own country.

## Other Important Information

### Our Policy Towards Children

The Services are for a general audience, and do not direct any content, products, or Services at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If you are a user between the ages of 13 and 18, you may only use Infogram through an account established by a parent or guardian, with that parent or guardian’s permission – provided that in your jurisdiction there is no requirement for you or your parent to provide any consent to Infogram for a minor’s use beyond what is already provided in Infogram’s Terms of Use and Privacy policy. By way of example, in some Designated Countries users as old as 16 may be required to have their parent or guardian submit a specific consent to Infogram, and in those countries users under 16 years of age may not use Infogram.

### Legal bases for processing (for Designated Countries) 

If you are a member or visitor in the Designated Countries, we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws. The primary legal basis for this is always your consent given when you sign up to our Services. The legal bases depend on the Services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only where:

  * We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Services;
  * It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services and to protect our legal rights and legitimate interests or those of third parties;
  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or
  * We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we or a third party (e.g. your employer) have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services.

If you have any questions about the lawful bases upon which we collect and use your personal data click here to learn how to get in touch with our Data Protection Officer.

### Contact Information

#### Questions or Comments

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns relating to the Infogram Service or this privacy policy, please send an email to [hello@infogram.com](mailto:hello@infogram.com) or write to us at:

Infogram  
Karen Tang  
450 Bryant Street  
San Francisco, CA 94107

We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
